<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seventh Workshop on Image Matching: Local Features &amp; Beyond</title>
    <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Seventh Workshop on Image Matching: Local Features &amp; Beyond</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2019/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 16th June 2019&#xA;Hyatt Regency A&#xA;Programme 08:45-09:00 Welcome (slides) 09:00-09:30 Amir Zamir (Stanford/UC Berkeley), Collection of Large-scale Densely-labeled 3D Data from the Real World Without a Single Click 09:30-10:15 Jiri Matas (CTU Prague), On the Art of Establishing Correspondence (slides) 10:15-11:00 Coffee Break &amp;amp; Poster Session 11:15-12:00 Torsten Sattler (Chalmers University of Technology), In Defense of Local Features for Visual Localization (slides) 12:00-12:15 IMW 2019 Challenge (slides) 12:15-12:30 Zixin Luo (HKUST), Winner of the Phototourism Challenge (slides) 12:30-12:45 Awards and Closing (slides) The workshop papers are available on CVF: link.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2020/</guid>
      <description>Important information Youtube livestream (free access) Schedule All times are PT (Pacific Time).&#xA;8:30-8:45: Welcome 8:45-9:30: Invited talk by Prof. Krystian Mikolajczyk (Imperial College London) 9:30-10:15: Invited talk by Prof. Dieter Fox (University of Washington) 10:15-10:30: Workshop paper, &amp;ldquo;Two-stage Discriminative Re-ranking for Large-scale Landmark Retrieval&amp;rdquo;, by Shuhei Yokoo (University of Tsukuba) 10:30-10:45: Workshop paper, &amp;ldquo;Match or No Match: Keypoint Filtering based on Matching Probability&amp;rdquo;, by Alexandra Papadaki (Technical University of Berlin) 10:45-11:15: Challenge introduction 11:15-11:30: Challenge results and discussion 11:30-13:45: Talks by challenge winners/participants (final schedule to be announced next week) 13:45-14:00: Closing About Traditional, keypoint-based formulations for image matching are still very competitive on tasks such as Structure from Motion (SfM), despite recent efforts on tackling pose estimation with dense networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2021/</guid>
      <description>Important information Livestream on YouTube The zoom link is listed on the CVPR website (registration required). Schedule All times are MT (Mountain Time). For convenience, 9AM MT corresponds to 8AM PT, 11AM ET, 5PM CET, and 11PM in China.&#xA;09:00-09:15: Welcome (full workshop slides) 09:15-10:00: Invited talk by Prof. Davide Scaramuzza (University of Zurich/ETH Zurich) 10:00-10:45: Invited talk by Prof. Marc Pollefeys (ETH Zurich/Microsoft) 10:45-11:00: Workshop paper talk by Daniel Koguciuk: &amp;ldquo;Perceptual Loss for Robust Unsupervised Homography Estimation&amp;rdquo; (paper | recording) 11:00-11:15: Workshop paper talk by Ufuk Efe: &amp;ldquo;DFM: A Performance Baseline for Deep Feature Matching&amp;rdquo; (paper | recording) 11:15-11:45: Challenge presentation (organizers) 11:45-12:15: Open discussion (organizers and participants) 12:15-13:35: Invited challenge talks (8 x 10 minutes — speakers/schedule to be confirmed soon) 12:15-12:25: Fabio Bellavia (University of Palermo) 12:25-12:35: Prune Truong (ETH Zurich) 12:35-12:45: Jiaming Sun/Xingyi He (Zhejiang University/SenseTime Research) 12:45-12:55: Wei Jiang (University of British Columbia) 12:55-13:05: Megvii Inc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2022/</guid>
      <description>Schedule 13:00-13:15&#x9;Welcome session INVITED TALKS&#xA;13:15-14:00&#x9;SuperPoint and SuperGlue: Lessons Learned (Tomasz Malisiewicz, Meta) ZOOM (slides) 14:00-14:45&#x9;Large-scale 3D reconstruction Deployment - Successes, Challenges, Open Problems (Aleš Hrabalík, Capturing Reality/Epic Games) LIVE BREAK&#xA;14:45-15:00&#x9;First coffee break + poster session WORKSHOP PAPER TALKS&#xA;15:00-15:10&#x9;Unstructured Object Matching using Co-Salient Region Segmentation (Alin-Ionut Popa, Amazon) LIVE 15:10-15:20&#x9;Nerfels: Renderable Neural Codes for Improved Camera Pose Estimation (Daniel DeTone, Meta) LIVE 15:20-15:30&#x9;Feature Query Networks: Neural Surface Description for Camera Pose Refinement (Hugo Germain, Ecole des Ponts ParisTech) LIVE (video) 15:30-15:40&#x9;Learning Co-segmentation by Segment Swapping for Retrieval and Discovery (Xi Shen, École des Ponts ParisTech) ZOOM (video) 15:40-15:50&#x9;DA-AE: Disparity-Alleviation Auto-Encoder Towards Categorization of Heritage Images for Aggrandized 3D Reconstruction (Dikshit Hegde, KLE Tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2023/</guid>
      <description>News! The 2023 Image Matching Challenge has been announced. We are happy to announce that the Fifth Workshop on Image Matching: Local Features and Beyond will be held at CVPR 2023 on June 19, 2023 (morning, Pacific Time) in Vancouver, Canada. The workshop will once again feature an open challenge which will be announced in the following weeks. We plan to hold it on Kaggle, as we did last year. Further details will be announced before the conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/cvpr2024/</guid>
      <description>We are happy to announce that the Sixth Workshop on Image Matching: Local Features and Beyond will be held at CVPR 2024 on June 17, 2024, in the afternoon, in Seattle, USA. The workshop will once again feature an open challenge on Kaggle. If you wish to receive announcements, please join our mailing list (expect 2-3 emails a year).&#xA;Schedule RECORDING&#xA;13:00 - 13:15: Welcome (organizers) 13:15 - 14:00: Invited talk by Prof.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakdown: Phototourism | MVS | Sequences</title>
      <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/breakdown/phototourism/mvs/by_seq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/breakdown/phototourism/mvs/by_seq/</guid>
      <description>Breakdown on the Phototourism dataset, multi-view stereo task, by sequence.&#xA;Back to the leaderboard MVS &amp;mdash; All sequences &amp;mdash; Sorted by mAP15o Method BM FCS LMS LB MC MR PSM RS SF SPC USC AVG Date Type By Details Link Contact Updated Descriptor size AKAZE (OpenCV)&#xA;kp:8000, match:nn 0.3576 0.4385 0.5551 0.3696 0.5935 0.3131 0.2543 0.4708 0.5709 0.6054 0.1847 0.4285 19-04-24 F Challenge organizers AKAZE, as implemented in OpenCV. Number of keypoints: 8000 per image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakdown: Phototourism | MVS | Subsets</title>
      <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/breakdown/phototourism/mvs/by_bag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/breakdown/phototourism/mvs/by_bag/</guid>
      <description>Breakdown on the Phototourism dataset, multi-view stereo task, by subset size.&#xA;Breakdown by bag size of 3 images Breakdown by bag size of 5 images Breakdown by bag size of 10 images Breakdown by bag size of 25 images Back to the leaderboard MVS, bag size 3 Method Date Type Ims (%) #Pts SR TL mAP5o mAP10o mAP15o mAP20o mAP25o ATE By Details Link Contact Updated Descriptor size AKAZE (OpenCV)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakdown: Phototourism | Stereo | Sequences</title>
      <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/breakdown/phototourism/stereo/by_seq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/breakdown/phototourism/stereo/by_seq/</guid>
      <description>Breakdown on the Phototourism dataset, multi-view stereo task, by sequence.&#xA;Back to the leaderboard Stereo &amp;mdash; All sequences &amp;mdash; Sorted by mAP15o Method BM FCS LMS LB MC MR PSM RS SF SPC USC AVG Date Type By Details Link Contact Updated Descriptor size AKAZE (OpenCV)&#xA;kp:8000, match:nn 0.0558 0.0133 0.0177 0.0575 0.0207 0.0112 0.0210 0.0329 0.0139 0.0102 0.0628 0.0288 19-04-24 F Challenge organizers AKAZE, as implemented in OpenCV. Number of keypoints: 8000 per image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMW CVPR 2019: Challenge</title>
      <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/challenge/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Local features have played a key role in a wide range of computer vision applications throughout the past 20 years, particularly since the introduction of SIFT.&#xA;Despite the drastic advancements resulting from deep learning techniques, 3D reconstruction under challenging conditions remains somewhat of an outlier, as performance in small, constrained benchmarks does not necessarily translate to real-world scenarios. In practice, keypoint-based methods remain the most common solution to this problem, and techniques such as SIFT or RANSAC are still very much in use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMW CVPR 2019: Leaderboard</title>
      <link>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/leaderboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://image-matching-workshop.github.io/leaderboard/</guid>
      <description>The challenge contains the following datasets and tasks (see this for details):&#xA;Task P1: Stereo maching in the &amp;lsquo;Phototourism&amp;rsquo; dataset Task P2: Multi-view reconstruction in the &amp;lsquo;Phototourism&amp;rsquo; dataset Task S1: Stereo maching in the &amp;lsquo;SILDa Image Matching&amp;rsquo; dataset Some notes:&#xA;Place the mouse cursor over row headers for details about the metrics (or here for an example). You can filter using the search box and labels, which are listed under the name of the method.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
